<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package Documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About the Package
================================
OpenShift is a platform as a service (PaaS) from Red Hat that is built on Docker and Kubernetes. Kubernetes is an open source, container as a service (CaaS) project originating from Google.

The core of the platform is containers and orchestration. For the container side of the house, the platform uses images based on the docker image format. For the orchestration side, it uses Kubernetes. 

This package provides means to interact with the Openshift system and performs different actions on it.
The user can either provide username/password or session token or certificate path as a means to login into the system. Any other combination will fail the action.

It creates a temporary config file in the temp directory. Every action first performs the login action which causes the session to be updated in the temporary config file and then it executes the action specific command. Once done with the action it logouts and this temporary config file will be deleted in the post process of every action.

=Setup=  
* Openshift command-line tool must be set in the environment

=Common Inputs=
* OpenShift server*:		     Provide OpenShift server name. E.g localhost:8443
* Username:			             Provide your OpenShift Login ID. E.g automic
* Password: 			             Provide your OpenShift Login Password.
* Session token:			     Provide your OpenShift session token for authentication to the API server.
* Certificate: 			             Provide the path to your crt file. 
* Skip SSL Validation:                   If Yes selected, it skips SSL Validation
* Sudo Username: 			     The username to be used for the sudo command. 
* Options: 			             Run using sudo password (and sudo username if specified).
* Sudo Password: 			     The password to be used for the sudo command.	
* Overwrite Agent:			     Overwrites the default agent
* Overwrite Login: 			     Overwrites the default login


=Actions=
Following actions are supported.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_PROJECT
* Action Description: This action is used to create a project in Openshift.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_RESOURCE
* Action Description: This action is used to create resource in Openshift.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.EXPOSE_SERVICE
* Action Description: This action looks up a service and exposes it as a route.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.REPLACE_RESOURCE
* Action Description: This action modifies an existing resource based on the contents of the specified configuration file.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_APP_FROM_SOURCE_CODE
* Action Description: This action is used to create application in openshift

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.SET_ENVIRONMENT_VARIABLES
* Action Description: This action is used to set environment variables in a build config or deployment config.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.UNSET_ENVIRONMENT_VARIABLES
* Action Description: This action is used to remove environment variables from build config or deployment config.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_APP_FROM_IMAGE
* Action Description: This action creates an application from the image.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_BUILDCONFIG_FROM_APP_SOURCE
* Action Description: This action creates a build configuration using application source code.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_OPENSHIFT.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_APP_FROM_TEMPLATE
* Action Description: This action creates an application using Openshift stored template or local template file.]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>